<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Qudsena</string>

    <string name="enable_DM">Enable Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="DM">Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="HQ">Statistics of demolitions in Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="txt_size">Text Size</string>
    <string name="txt_news">Trending</string>
    <string name="txt_video">View our all Videos</string>
    <string name="txt_all">View All</string>
    <string name="txt_change">Change Language</string>
    <string name="txt_playlist">Playlists</string>
    <string name="video_one">With the stationed Hanadi 1</string>
    <string name="video_four">With the stationed Hanadi 2</string>
    <string name="video_five">Jerusalem flashes - season two -</string>
    <string name="video_five_title">House demolition / Jerusalem information, Absentees’ property law / Jerusalem information, Judaism / Jerusalem information, Jerusalem among the Jews / Jerusalem information, the Temple among the Jews / Jerusalem information, Crusades / Jerusalem information, Poverty of Jerusalemites / Jerusalem information, building permits / Jerusalem information</string>
    <string name="video_two">Joseph and Mary - Season One -</string>
    <string name="video_three">Holy Flashes - Season Three -</string>
    <string name="video_four_title">With the stationed Hanadi, the second season, the sixth episode - the blue identity, with the stationed Hanadi, the second season, the fifth episode, the Moroccan Gate, a program with the stationed Hanadi, the second season, the eighth episode - real estate leaks, with the stationed Hanadi, the second season, the third episode - Rabat and the Golden List, with the stationed Hanadi season The second, the seventh episode - Al-Fath Al-Salahi, with the stationed Hanadi, the second season, the fourth episode - the economic restriction, with the stationed Hanadi, the second season, the first episode - the Bab al-Rahma chapel, with the stationed Hanadi, the second season, the second episode - Christians and Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="video_three_title">Judaization - Jerusalem information, Moria plateau - Jerusalem information, one sanctuary - sacred information, the chapel of the prophets - Jerusalem information, not a sanctuary - Jerusalem information, what is the Al-Aqsa Mosque - Jerusalem information, temporal and spatial division - sacred information, the relationship of the Holy Mosque to the Al-Aqsa Mosque</string>
    <string name="video_two_title">Joseph and Mary - the history of Jerusalem, Joseph and Mary - the name of the Al-Aqsa Mosque, Joseph and Mary - what is Al-Aqsa Mosque?, Joseph and Mary - the excavations of Al-Aqsa Mosque, Joseph and Mary - the features of Al-Aqsa Mosque, Joseph and Mary - the relationship of Al-Aqsa Mosque to the Grand Mosque, Joseph and Mary - Virtues Al-Aqsa Mosque, Joseph and Mary - Virtues of Al-Aqsa Mosque 2</string>
    <string name="video_one_title">The names of the Al-Aqsa Mosque with the stationed Hanadi, the reality of the Al-Aqsa Mosque with the stationed Hanadi, the Judaization of Jerusalem with the stationed Hanadi, the Arnona tax with the stationed Hanadi, the temporal division with the stationed Hanadi, the Marwani prayer hall with the stationed Hanadi, the old city and its divisions with the stationed Hanadi, the sanctity of the Al-Aqsa Mosque with the stationed Hanadi Hanadi</string>
    <string name="txt_far">Report your distance from Al-Aqsa Mosque</string>
    <string name="txt_more">Read more</string>
    <string name="video">Videos</string>
    <string name="details">The Israeli occupation authorities classified four types of house demolitions:

1- Military demolition: It is the demolition of homes by the Israeli occupation army for military reasons (under the pretext of protecting soldiers and settlements); Although most of the inhabitants of these houses are innocent; However, Israel justifies these actions in the name of “legal military objectives.” This type of demolition does not apply to the situation of Silwan only; Rather, it is prevalent throughout the West Bank and Area C.


2- Punitive demolition: It is the demolition of Palestinian families’ homes by the Israeli occupation army under the pretext of their children carrying out military operations against the Israelis. This type of demolition has no military objectives. Returning to the Fourth Geneva Convention, Article 33: No protected person may be punished for a crime he did not personally commit; Thus, "punitive demolition" contradicts the statute of this treaty and Article 50 of the decisions of the "Hague Regulations".
3- Administrative demolition: It is the most common, and this decision is implemented under the pretext of building without obtaining a license, or under the pretext of the public interest (as some cases appear in the Al-Bustan neighborhood). The ease of issuing the administrative decision for demolition lies in the fact that the municipality engineer issues a report in these cases. while the mayor, in turn, signs it; Although "construction without permits" is also common in the settlements.
4- Judicial demolition: It is a judicial decision issued by the Israeli courts, including: the Local Affairs Court, the Central Court, and the Supreme Court. The judicial demolition decision usually comes after the completion of administrative procedures and decisions issued by the Jerusalem municipality.
It is forbidden, according to the basic principle of the Judicial Demolition Law, to punish an individual for an act he or she has not personally done; (Also, there is no provision in the Israeli Penal Code that authorizes the Israeli authorities to impede individuals for the actions of other individuals, which is in line with the principle that provides for the personalization of punishment (individual punishment).</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
</resources>